<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Super!Store Documentation</title>
    <link>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Super!Store Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Descriptions and links</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/descriptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/descriptions/</guid>
      <description>Descriptions and links Describe your game with an impressive tagline and description. The descriptions help you stand out from the mass of games.
Tagline A tagline is displayed on a store page. The tagline provides a summary of a web page. Search engines show this page description in search results.
It’s not a technical limit, but you can take into account, that the description length depends on the display width, search engine and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Settings</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/general/</guid>
      <description>Store presence Super!Store allows you to create and adjust the content of your store page.
    General data  Go to your game&amp;rsquo;s store page on General tab to fill in the general data:
  Game title
 Developers (multiple values separated by commas)
 Publishers (multiple values separated by commas)
      Next steps   TODO  Questions? Support We are always happy to help with a code, improve a guide or consider a feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Settings</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/media/</guid>
      <description>Media A quality game matters the most but screenshots play an important role in the success of your game too.
Your game images can be displayed on all devices including 4K and Retina displays. After uploading images, we will automatically resize it for Full HD and other displays.
Cover image The cover image is used as a special featuring block on the store home page at the very top of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supported Languages</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/languages/</guid>
      <description> Supported Languages  Go to your game&amp;rsquo;s store page on General tab to select the languages:
     Next steps   TODO  Questions? Support We are always happy to help with a code, improve a guide or consider a feature.  GitHub Super!Store is an open-source digital distribution platform for game developers and publishers.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags Features Genre</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.qilin.super.com/docs/tags/</guid>
      <description>Help customers quickly search your game Super!Store uses tags, genres and features to make customers relevant search. It will be listed in the navigation menu above the name of your product, also in filters. Depending on it, Super!Store shows your game in the similar games block.
Tags Select the most applicable meanings to your game. Top 10 tags will help customers find your game from a mass of similar genres.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>